{
    "id": "9dee9b28a4fe4885831debce3ccffa31",
    "title": "Connecting Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was angry ……………………….. they hadn’t invited her to their party.",
            "description": "Because gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "so",
                "therefore"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29d0d57d6d0c4cfeaba8167e6c2f7dd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… you don’t deliver the project on time, they will cancel the contract.",
            "description": "If expresses a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Until",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dffe4b4df3a9471ba2d2bee74c05a0b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… he is lame, he walks with great difficulty.",
            "description": "Both as and because give the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "If",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2ed9a31cbf3742d7bf80200ed0d1690f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is neither intelligent ………………………. hardworking.",
            "description": "The correct conjunction is neither/nor.",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5f8b359a7a64dbeb885b0ec5f9effa0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will not permit this …………………………… you kill me.",
            "description": "Even if refers to the future even though refers to the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "even if",
                "even though",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9f186a6f7e540f887ed7f59eb4c18e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "You cannot go ……………………….. you have finished that report.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with a slight difference of meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "until",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ede493abffe84aa989a34bb5a14e0c29"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. she doesn’t like you, why are you still chasing her?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Whether",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6da9cf49cee43e5a9aa9fec03a24adf"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… I worked day and night, I couldn’t meet the deadline.",
            "description": "Even though refers to the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "Even though",
                "Even if",
                "As if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c4e94f78a144e07ba4c32ef5b63a434"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………. beautiful that every guy in the neighborhood wants to marry her.",
            "description": "Use so before an adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4470bd23f6024f51913d2e85121b37a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The higher you go, ………………………… it gets.",
            "description": "The comparative is used in both clauses in this structure. ",
            "answers": [
                "the colder",
                "the more cold",
                "colder"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f148e3eb9b347f6af770db7ffb5a449"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. she is very beautiful, she has hardly any friends.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f586398cb3e44b2a81de7eaa0482446"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house …………………………. Lincoln was born.",
            "description": "Where means in which. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where",
                "there"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ab48769bcbd490bb934c9407d68fe07"
        }
    ]
}